Thank you for watching.
Yes, please.
Let me introduce you a little bit.
This is Kyokuchan Risas. Please give my best regards.
Okay, that's it.
Okay, let's go to the playback.
Okay, here comes the playback.
Let's go to the playback.
Yes, we'll go to playback.
Yes, cuttout!
Thank you for your time!
Please jump.
Please jump wrong.
One, two, three, four, five.
Maybe even a little light jumping, like now.
Like Mr. Kasugi.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
Do you laugh?
No.
I'm being filmed, right?
It's been a while since I've seen the making of a film.
Here you go.
Thank you for waiting.
It's over.
It's been a while since I've danced.
Um, what's the word?
The sister who tells me, what do you call her? Staff?
I thought I've seen her before, but I was right, she was in Voyager.
The same person worked on the production of Ebiri's last music video.
Yes, let's start!Yes, start!
Cute! It's cute! I think it's good!
It's OK!
I'll go to the next part. I have to go to the next one.
I forgot my shoes!
I'm sorry, I forgot a lot of things.
Please.
More, oh no! I'm out!
Caw!
I feel like a gal.
Let's go.
Good morning.
Interview.
What do you think? It's just the chorus.
Is it okay if I look at you this way?
Please.
Sorry, one more question.
How do you like it when you dance it?
Dancing?
It's been a long time since I've danced in a white space, or rather, it's been about half a year since I've danced in a music video.
So I was a little nervous,
I was a little bit nervous, and since I was the only one in the music video this time, I was in the center.
I felt a little strange about that, and I am feeling a little pressured.
How long have you been dancing?
I have been dancing since I was in the fourth grade of elementary school,
Since I was in the fourth grade of elementary school,
I think I was 8 or 9 years old.
So I have been dancing for about 15 years this year.
But my first dance class was hip-hop jazz,
But I also did idol work for a while,
So I did end up doing a lot of idol dance,
But I have been dancing for less than 15 years.
Is the video itself different from dancing?
Yes, it is.Yes, sir.
What do you think?
First of all, there is nothing idol-like about it.
There is no "spread out like this," as is often the case with idols,
There are no angles.
I'm a little nervous because the focus is on how to dance in a cool way.
Well, there are a few songs.
I'm not sure if you can keep up with the game now.
I didn't catch this one.
You can watch.
Noor click.
I'm sorry.
You can just say that, can't you? It doesn't matter what it looks like.
It's not wrong, right? Let's do it.
You're going to love it.
Oh, yeah.
All those notes.
Minus one.
You can do it, can't you? It doesn't matter what it is, does it?
It's not wrong. Let's do it.
Okay, that's it.
Let's go again.
Whatever it is, I made a mistake.
So it's the second half.
I've memorized the lyrics by now.
I don't know, some of the lyrics are the same in some parts and not in others.
You have lyrics?
Well, they are the same in the first and second verse, the same in the second and third verse, the same in the first and third verse, and so on, and so on.
And not all of them are the same.
I was misled by the fact that they were all the same.
It's like my mouth thinks it's the same.
How can I learn how to remember?
Can you give me some tips on how to remember?
Memorization.
Memorize the lending card.Memorize the lending card.
I'm memorizing it by eye now, too.
Yes, I am.
Thank you very much.
Well, I'm a little nervous, aren't I?
Are you okay? I'm trying to remember.
I'll do my best.
I'll stop you if you make a mistake.
Because, you know? If I keep dancing until the end and make a mistake, it will only be a burden for everyone.
I think I'm going to make a mistake.
I'm really going to make a mistake.
That's right! I'll stop immediately.
You said you would have made a mistake in singing if you had gone this way.
That's what I always say. I always say that.
If I make a mistake, I stop immediately.
The photographer's function ensures
M whites B
You know what, just point the camera in my direction, so I'm just going to shoot here for now.
I thought I'd shoot it. It's better than the real thing.
Hey.
Why are you doing that?
Everyone's trying to get on camera.
Okay, okay.
Can I ask you to leave?
I'm leaving.
All right.
Good night.
Okay.
Oh!
It's not a fisheye.
Just do it normally.
Oh! It's okay.
Whisper it.
I got the whisper line.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Let's cut.
Here's the cut.
I'll come in closer with this.
And cut.
That's it.
And that's it.
That's all for now. That's all for the music video.
So, the shooting of my first music video as a solo artist has come to an end.
At the end, I felt like it was really over.
What's this?
Confetti
Silver confetti
I think we had a lot of fun with all the different English words we used.
Of course, it was the first time for me to shoot a music video by myself.
It was a strange feeling to be in the center for the rest of my life.
I had a different sense of responsibility, but it was a lot of fun.
It was a lot of fun, and it all happened so fast.
I can't wait to see the finished product!
Thank you very much!